http://www.pplmotorhomes.com/privacy-policy

CLOSE MENURVs for SaleAll VehiclesClass A MotorhomesClass C & B MotorhomesDiesel MotorhomesFifth WheelsToy HaulersTravel TrailersView AllSell My RVTrade RVParts SuperstoreElectrical, Plumbing & LP GasEntertainment, Comfort & CampingMaintenance & HardwareRV AppliancesTowing, Hitches, Jacks, ChassisView AllFree Booklet!About UsContact UsPrivacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you place an order or fill out a form.
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following
ways:
To
improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer
service requests and support needs)To
process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged,
transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever,
without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the
purchased product or service requested by the customer.
To send
periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, may be
used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in
addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related
product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future
emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each
email.How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request or place an order.
These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies except to gain knowledge that will help us improve the effectiveness of our website.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.CAN-SPAM Compliance
We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on June 1, 2009
Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Mail to:Diana LeBlanc10777 Southwest FreewayHouston, Texas 77074United States1-800-755-4775
Email:Privacy Policy Customer Pledge
We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:Federal Trade
Commission FairCalifornia Online Privacy Protection ActChildren's Online Privacy Protection ActPrivacy AllianceControlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act
If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form.
Respectfully,
Diana LeblancPresidentwww.pplmotorhomes.com

